<post>
<link>http://www.ldswomensbookreview.com/wordpress/2011/08/22/all-diets-work-by-jen-brewer-rd-blog-tour/</link>
<time>1314041847</time>
<content>2006 Podcasts · 2007 Podcasts · 2008 Podcasts · 2009 Podcasts · 2010 Podcasts · Special Features · Blog Tours · Contests · Countdown to Christmas · Countdown to Summer · LDStorymakers &amp; Whitney Awards · Teaser Tuesdays · To-Read Tuesday · Weekend Reading .... Maggie Fechner · Margaret Turley · Marsha Ward · Melanie Jacobson · Natalie Palmer · Nichole Giles · Rebecca Irvine · Rebecca Talley · Ronda Gibb Hinrichsen · Shannon Alder · Shirley Bahlmann · Tamara Hart Heiner ...</content>
<nick>podcast@ldswomensbookreview.com (LDSWBR)</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://thestar.blogs.com/tiff/2011/08/canuck-sci-fi-horror-and-fantasy-costume-design-at-tiff.html</link>
<time>1314041393</time>
<content>... including a rare behind-the-scenes look at the creation of the character Dren in Vincenzo Natali&#39;s Splice with creature designer Amro Attia and costume designer Alex Kavanagh on Oct. 12 at 7 p.m. There are also special guided tours, ...</content>
<nick>Toronto Star</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://travelasia.living-101.com/travel-asia/classic-package-travel-to-egypt-8-nights-9-days/</link>
<time>1314041350</time>
<content>Tour Guides: All our tour Guided tours in Cairo are at least competent Egyptologist 5 years experience. They also have academic qualifications to make your turn so successful. E-mail : nataly@egypttravelhotdeals.com ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://northernvirginiahomesandcondos.blogspot.com/2011/08/youre-invited-to-credit-class.html</link>
<time>1314040860</time>
<content>Just Reduced - 8184 E. Main Street - Marshall · Please Welcome Natalie Martinez To Our Team · You&#39;re Invited to an Open House Tuesday from 11:30... Chip Miller Electric to 2011 GPAAR Board of Direct. ... Prince William, and Fauquier Counties home and this website offers home buyers and home sellers a superior comparative market analysis (CMA), a way to view real estate and MLS IDX listings including virtual tours, prepare your home for sale, and more. ...</content>
<nick>Chip and Becky Miller</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.kusadasiobserver.com/?p=1214</link>
<time>1314040731</time>
<content>... ibiza flights, ibiza holidays, ibiza tours, Identi.ca, indianpad, insurance, international movers, Internetmedia, invest in turkey, iran, izmir, izmir flights, izmir flighys, jewellery in kusadasi, jobs in kusadasi, jobs in turkey, jobs in turkey for british people ... DE, mixx, MOB, monarch flights, Moscow, mothers day, mothers day in turkey, move to kusadaso, moving to kusadasi, MSNReporter, muti, MyShare, myspace, N4G, natalie cassidy, natalie cassidy in turkey ...</content>
<nick>Kusadasi News</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://acwr.net/arts-notes/arts-notes-august-23-2011/</link>
<time>1314038751</time>
<content>SB Contemporary Art and Canada South Eco Tours present an art exhibition titled, I like to ride my bicycle…. this coming August 13 to September 11, 2011. This exhibition called on artists and the community of all ages to come forward with ... Liana Loduca, Shelley Martin, Karlene Neilsen, Alina Petrichyn, Walter Petrichyn, Victor Romao, Matthew Santoro, Natalie Santoro, Djordje Srdanov, Sanja Srdanov, Vanessa Sheilds, Natalie Sinn, Gulnaz Turdalieva plus many more… ...</content>
<nick>ED</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://moviemonger.net/2011/08/22/the-dvd-wrapup-something-borrowed-jane-eyre-cul-de-sac-queen-to-play-meet-monica-velour-big-lebowski/</link>
<time>1314037228</time>
<content>The Blu-ray edition includes the featurettes, “On Location Tours,” in which author and some of her fans ride around New York in a tour bus, talking about the movie, the book and the characters; “Inside &#39;Something Borrowed,&#39;” a making-of ..... and archetypes from 100 years of westerns. try to imagine “The Searchers,” if Natalie Wood had been abducted by vampires, instead of Indians, and John Wayne had laser weapons in his arsenal and a souped-up motorcycle in his stable. ...</content>
<nick>неизвестен</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://memphis-news.info/memphis-top-stories/idx-solution-simplifies-online-real-estate-search-for-memphis-area-buyers.html</link>
<time>1314036425</time>
<content>Mortgage calculators, virtual tours, mapping technology and scheduling options are all conveniently available on the website of Helton. These tools and features allow home seekers to narrow and focus their search throughout the MAARMLS. ...</content>
<nick>MemphisNews</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.exclusivemembers.com/country-singer-chely-wright-marries-girlfriend/</link>
<time>1314031603</time>
<content>By On Top Magazine Staff Country music singer Chely Wright has said the United Service Organizations (USO) stopped inviting her to participate in overseas tours to entertain the troops since she came out gay. ...</content>
<nick>неизвестен</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://moj-kruiz.ru/gde-uznat-vse-o-turrynke-sibiri</link>
<time>1314030715</time>
<content>Сегодня о своем участии в “ТУРФЕСТ-2011″ уже заявили: Anex Tour, Coral Travel, Danko Travel Company, DSBW-Tours, Pac Group, Pegas Touristik, S7 Tour, Sunmar, Tez Tour, “Интурист”, “Натали Турс”, авиакомпании “Сибирь” и “Трансаэро”. ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://heavytable.com/chicken-coop-tours-and-august-22-tweet-rodeo/</link>
<time>1314030658</time>
<content>Chicken Coop Tours and August 22 Tweet Rodeo. @magicbushotdogs is one of three food trucks recommended by The Star Tribune, @fultonmarketmn shares a New York Times article on farmers market competition, today @blacksheeppizza in St. ...</content>
<nick>Hannah Rogal</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://healthyvoyager.com/2.0/2011/08/22/healthy-voyager-radio-%E2%80%93-getting-fiscally-fit/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=healthy-voyager-radio-%25e2%2580%2593-getting-fiscally-fit</link>
<time>1314025237</time>
<content>Healthy Voyager Radio · The Healthy Voyager Tour Bus Show · The Healthy Voyager Travel Show · The Healthy Voyager&#39;s Global Kitchen Show · Travel · Adventure · Attractions · City Secrets · Healthy Voyager Tours · Restaurant Reviews ... Featuring guests Natalie Bovis-Nelsen, The Liquid Muse &amp; Caroline MacDougall, creator of Teeccino... Filed Under: Healthy Voyager Radio, Shows &amp; Podcasts Tagged With: career, children, diet, eco, entertainment, financial, green, guests, ...</content>
<nick>HealthyVoyager</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.thenextjourney.com/2011/08/waitomo-glowworms-caves-bushwalks/</link>
<time>1314025200</time>
<content>A few quick pointers that were immediately observed: 1) The turn signal and windshield wipers are swapped, so Natalie always knew when I planned on changing lanes because the wipers suddenly began flying across the windshield. ... The trips were both led by exceptional guides (Lucas and Mark) and both tours only had 5 people, including us. The intimate nature of these trips made them so much more enjoyable and the guides seemed to have even more fun as they could tailor ...</content>
<nick>Darin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://natalieast.com/?p=389</link>
<time>1314023623</time>
<content>Sibonney also founded Relish Culinary tours, a company that offers intimate dining experiences in Spain and Italy. Sibonney founded her business after she traveled in Spain, and created relationships with the country&#39;s (and even the ...</content>
<nick>Natalie Ast</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://creativecase.wordpress.com/2011/08/22/adventurneers-take-on-the-coronation-double-century-cycle-race/</link>
<time>1314019439</time>
<content>Tags: adventure, Adventurneers, axis house, barrydale, coronation double century, cycle tours, cycling, cycling tours south africa, cycling western cape, daytrippers, endurance cycling, karoo cycling, ladies cycle team, road cycling ...</content>
<nick>CreativeImagineer</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.bambinogoodies.co.uk/cool-theatre-the-tiger-who-came-to-tea-london/</link>
<time>1314018017</time>
<content>August 22, 2011 by Natalie · Leave a Comment. The Tiger Who came to Tea- the Official Trailer. The Tiger Who Came To Tea. High on the list of my daughters favourite stories, The Tiger Who Came to Tea by Judith Kerr has been capturing ...</content>
<nick>Natalie</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.5dom.com/?p=5824</link>
<time>1314017681</time>
<content>Natalie Coughlin, a United States swimmer, is a favorite to win several medals at the 2008 Beijing Olympic Games. She already has experienced Olympic success, as she won 5 medals (2 gold, 2 silver, and 1 bronze) at the 2004 Olympics in ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.intercot.com/discussion/showthread.php?t=184982</link>
<time>1314016514</time>
<content>Hey, Natalie, I&#39;ll be down there with you (though arriving a couple of days earlier). We&#39;ll have to meet up to say hi. In general, my experience with this time frame is that crowds are pretty manageable up until around Dec 19 or 20 then ...</content>
<nick>DisneyNut6777</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.themartellexperience.com/2011/08/22/ecommunity-update-efficiency-nb-announces-first-two-homes-qualify-for-net-zero-incentive/</link>
<time>1314016348</time>
<content>The Martell Home Builders EcoPlusHome ECOmmunity will be open for public tours Sundays from 2-4pm. For a private tour please contact Natalie Davison at 506-232-1276 or natalie@themartellexperience.com ...</content>
<nick>ndavison</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://pajamasmedia.com/instapundit/126633/</link>
<time>1314015565</time>
<content>He&#39;s a Marine Corps veteran who served two tours in Iraq. A former city councilman in Lyndhurst, a suburb of Cleveland, he led the fight for the first property tax rollback in the county&#39;s history. As a state legislator, ...</content>
<nick>Glenn Reynolds</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://theadbuzz.com/2011/08/crossing-the-line/</link>
<time>1314015304</time>
<content>Posted by Patrice-Natalie James on August 22nd, 2011. No Comments. Tweet. Hundreds and hundreds of ads are seen by millions of people, but what happens when an ad is deemed offensive? An advertisement needs to be memorable, witty, ...</content>
<nick>Patrice-Natalie James</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://backofthebookreviews.com/2011/08/bertena-varney-%E2%80%93-the-lure-of-the-vampire-blog-tour-guest-post/</link>
<time>1314014436</time>
<content>Fallen Review · The Betrayal of Natalie Hargrove Review · Torment Review · Louise Deacon · Twilight, True Love and You: Seven Secrets to Finding Your Edward or Jacob Review · Lynne Bradbury · The Ugly Duckling Review · Maggie Stiefvater ...</content>
<nick>Ashley</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://savidgereads.wordpress.com/2011/08/22/reading-with-authors-3-valley-of-the-dolls-%E2%80%93-jacqueline-susann-with-paul-magrs/</link>
<time>1314012640</time>
<content>She went on TV and book tours – but she also did things like taking breakfast and coffee to the lorry drivers who were transporting her books around the US. It has sold insanely well over the decades and I say, rather than a cult value, ...</content>
<nick>savidgereads</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.itcultura.com/2011/08/resenha-nao-sou-este-tipo-de-garota-siobhan-vivian/</link>
<time>1314010843</time>
<content>A vida é sobre suas decisões e escolhas, e Natalie Sterling se orgulha de sempre fazer as melhores. Ela ignora os caras populares e babacas da escola, sempre ganha medalhas de honra e está prestes a ser a primeira estudante jovem a ser ...</content>
<nick>Kel</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://musicmattersblog.com/2011/08/22/monday-mailbag-business-types/</link>
<time>1314010824</time>
<content>Filed under: Business Issues,Monday Mailbag,Studio Ideas — natalie @ 6:00 am. As I contemplate venturing out into the World Wide Web, I&#39;m thinking I should change my business structure from a Sole Proprietorship to an LLC for liability ...</content>
<nick>natalie</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://tvoj-otdyh.ru/expotravel-2011-gde-projdet-vystavka-v-etom-godu</link>
<time>1314008760</time>
<content>Так, в числе постоянных участников крупнейшие туроператорские компании, среди которых Natalie Tours, Pegas Touristik, Coral Travel, Tez Tour, PAC Group, Danko Travel Company, “НТК Интурист”, Ascent Travel, “Мир” и другие. ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.sheistoofondofbooks.com/2011/08/22/book-review-get-me-out-of-here-by-henry-sutton/</link>
<time>1314007238</time>
<content>Joy Weese Moll: Sounds wonderful -- I never thought about eggplants with chi... natalie @book, line, and sinker: i&#39;ve been considering a csa for two years now but think i wo... Serena: I&#39;m not an eggplant eater, so this wouldn&#39;t be for ...</content>
<nick>sheistoofondofbooks</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://astheysawit.com/16770-1991-music.html?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=1991-music</link>
<time>1314006893</time>
<content>Both the St. Louis Symphony and the New York Philharmonic canceled European tours due to the Persian Gulf War. In a dramatic gesture of solidarity, Zubin Mehta, then music director of both the New York Philharmonic and the Israel ..... First up was Natalie Cole, an accomplished R &amp; B singer who recorded a tribute album to her late father, Nat King Cole. That set, called Unforgettable, rode at No. 1 on the pop album chart for five weeks and sold more than 2 million units. ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://foodgloriousfoodoc.blogspot.com/2011/08/bringing-out-big-guns.html</link>
<time>1314003780</time>
<content>Such was the case when our friend, Phil came back from Iraq, after flying Blackhawk helicopters after one of his several tours of duty for the Army. Phil is a supremely awesome guy... so a bunch of us winos got together (some coming ...</content>
<nick>V</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.capturemoi.net/how-to-get-copied-oscar-dresses/</link>
<time>1314000285</time>
<content>Some of their copied celebrities from Oscar night consist of: Kate Winslet, Sarah Jessica Parker, Angelina Jolie, Natalie Portman and Heidi Klum. They take great pride in offering the typical lady celebrity-style attire that she are ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://britneyspearsnewsong.mobilni.mobi/112/order-and-get-weber-bbq-for-the-loved-ones-computer-repair-articles/</link>
<time>1313997718</time>
<content>TRAVEL TROLL – Travel News – Deals – Hotels – Airlines – Tours … Luxury health and wellness resort Chiva-Som has announced its Winter Wellness Specials for the lean season, ending 30 September, 2011.? Chiva-Som is the perfect winter escape, ... When Hesher, starring Natalie Portman and Joseph Gordon-Levitt, arrived at the 2010 Sundance Film Festival, it generated a fair amount of buzz. Unfortunately, when it was finally released in theaters last week, it didn&#39;t take off. ...</content>
<nick>supercenter</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://calcuttawalks.wordpress.com/2011/08/22/natgeos-fox-history-and-traveller-shoots-north-calcutta/</link>
<time>1313992329</time>
<content>... April 2009, February 2009, September 2008, August 2008, May 2008, February 2008, January 2008, December 2007, November 2007, September 2007. Categories. Random · Uncategorized. Blogroll. Natalie Buda Smith · V3 Travels and Tours ...</content>
<nick>calcuttawalks</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://livegolfvideos.com/pga-tour-confidential-playoff-storylines/</link>
<time>1313988579</time>
<content>Ai Miyazato Videos · Anna Rawson Videos · Cristie Kerr Videos · Natalie Gulbis Videos · Yani Tseng Videos · Jim Furyk Videos · Lee Westwood Videos · Luke Donald Videos · Martin Kaymer Videos · Moe Norman · Padraig Harrington · Paul Casey Videos ... Golf.com: Tours &amp; News. From Live Golf Videos/Golf News, post PGA Tour Confidential: Playoff Storylines. Post Footer automatically generated by wp-posturl plugin for wordpress. VN:F [1.9.10_1130]. please wait. ...</content>
<nick>Live Golf Videos</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://fanmania.info/?p=49020</link>
<time>1313987045</time>
<content>... but still i didn&#39;t think much about her either way. but after she started promo tours for her show, she suddenely came off as a pretty, but crazy, nitwit. her show is supposed to show how normal she is, but she&#39;s as nutty as a bag ...</content>
<nick>Ultimate Fan</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.pravasitoday.com/paes-bhupati-win-cincinnati-title</link>
<time>1313986870</time>
<content>The No.3 seeds in the women&#39;s doubles, American Vania King and her Kazakhstan partner Yaroslava Shvedova, outlasted unseeded Natalie Grandin from South Africa and Vladmira Uhlirova of the Czech republic to take their first title of the ...</content>
<nick>pravasitoday</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://moj-kruiz.ru/intriga-po-arabski-ili-kto-eshhe-zadumal-letat-iz-kolcovo-v-oae</link>
<time>1313986641</time>
<content>Намерения добавить третью частоту уже обозначила и авиакомпания flydubai, и, по словам Олега Хигера, директора по продажам Natalie Tours (основного блочника туроператора), окончательно данный вопрос будет решен в течение ближайшего ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.vacationpackagesdeals.org/2011/0822/discover-egypt-and-jordan-travel-package-11-nights-12-days/</link>
<time>1313986082</time>
<content>Discover and visit Cairo, Aswan, Luxor with her in the tours, Wadi Rum and Petra city in the legend, which has become one of the wonders of the world. Enjoy. ... All a guides have been associating Egyptologist as well as with during slightest 5 years experience. In addition, they have a educational education to have your revisit so successful. : nataly@egypttravelhotdeals.com : www.egypttravelhotdeals.com transport packages. days, Discover, Egypt, Jordan, nights, package, ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://lifebehindthewall.wordpress.com/2011/08/22/our-visit-to-hermudu-historical-ruins/</link>
<time>1313984034</time>
<content>China Traveling. China Flights · China Tours ... natalie on The Definition of a Beauty in… lifebehindthewall on RE: Controversial Article on C… Stan on RE: Controversial Article on C… 10 Common Chinese He… on My Trip To The Traditional Chi… ShaSha LaPerf on Agenda Magazine interview · lifebehindthewall on Agenda Magazine interview · Harleyq2 on Agenda Magazine interview · Gregory Young on Agenda Magazine interview · Deb on Agenda Magazine interview ...</content>
<nick>lifebehindthewall</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.elephantjournal.com/2011/08/why-heartbreak-is-the-best-thing-your-yoga-has-ever-had-an-interview-with-bhakti-yogi-sara-ivanhoe/</link>
<time>1313983189</time>
<content>SI: You know, what keeps popping into my mind is my friend Krishna Das, many of you know Krishna Das, it&#39;s through his beautiful chanting that he tours around the country and I met him 15 years ago, 17 years ago something like this, ...</content>
<nick>Lilly Bechtel</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://pajamasmedia.com/instapundit/126592/</link>
<time>1313981344</time>
<content>Bob Hope was an American icon, the only person ever named an honorary veteran of the US Armed Forces for decades of USO tours that have won praise from everyone from John Steinbeck to Bill Clinton, a man who could sing with Bing Crosby, ...</content>
<nick>Glenn Reynolds</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.g-webmarketing.com/websiteseo/uncategorized/apartments-in-charlotte-nc-33</link>
<time>1313980812</time>
<content>There are one, two and three bedroom floor plans luxury or income based apartments – adjust the pricing to suit your needs property listings with videos, virtual tours, and photos apartment amenities, community features, ...</content>
<nick>AdminXML-RPC</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://online-video-chat.com/blog/view/id_72910</link>
<time>1313979504</time>
<content>Big blu ray season names like Natalie Portman and Scarlett Johansson were tossed around, but it&#39;s relative newcomer Rooney Mar锟?who&#39;s landed the coveted role of the badass bisexual hacker in &quot;The Girl with the Dragon Tattoo&quot; and its ...</content>
<nick>неизвестен</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.away-team.com/rock/2011/08/interview-machine-heads-dave-mcclain-from-gaga-to-dub-step-to-the-heaviest-fucking-metal-machine-head-has-made/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=interview-machine-heads-dave-mcclain-from-gaga-to-dub-step-to-the-heaviest-fucking-metal-machine-head-has-made</link>
<time>1313977599</time>
<content>That are really band friendly and people like John Reese the guy that puts this thing on (John Reese is co-creator of Rockstar Mayhem Fest) loves metal, he tours with the festival, gets the bands together and has theme parties during the tour for ..... There is a long list of people to thank for making this and all of our Mayhem Fest interviews happen, so, forgive me if I forgot anyone, but thanks to Lilly at Roadrunner, Bill at eOne Music, Rikki, Natalie, and Jessica at ...</content>
<nick>Slim Jim Keller</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://tvoj-otdyh.ru/vecherinka-obrazov</link>
<time>1313975816</time>
<content>4 раза не вылетевшие туристы, а также рейсы в Испанию через Польшу · Швейцарские приключения российских турагентов · Чили: не забудьте посетить сердце Сантьяго · Черно-белый стул для Natalie Tours · Хочешь весело провести День смеха? ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://country.sing-we.com/2011/08/21/day-tour-to-luxor-and-valley-of-kings-from-safaga-port/</link>
<time>1313975407</time>
<content>-All transportation by air-conditioned vehicle in Safaga port and Luxor -Admission fees to the sightseeing in Luxor as per itinerary -Lunch during Luxor tour at a local restaurant in Luxor -Professional Egyptologist English speaking tour guide -Drop off service from your Ship terminal in Safaga port. Tour Excludes: - Optional tours - Personal expenses. www.egypttravelhotdeals.com. Nataly - About the Author: Posted by billgood Country Singing Subscribe to RSS feed ...</content>
<nick>billgood</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://rentalfor.net/party-rentals/birthday-party-ideas-that-are-high-energy/</link>
<time>1313974225</time>
<content>Tamarack Canopy Zip Line Tours: (208) 325-1006 or tamarackzipline.com. Fee is $99 per person in addition to tax. Natalie Bartley authored the Boise&#39;s Best Outdoor Adventures mobile app, existing by iTunes, and two route guidebooks. ...</content>
<nick>rich</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://tandemgeek.wordpress.com/2011/08/21/tandeming-through-the-eyes-of-a-14-year-old/</link>
<time>1313974094</time>
<content>Our long-time friend Mark Johnson from Precision Tandems in Kansas shared a couple of web journals written by his daughter Courtney who, along with sister Natalie, have truly grown-up on tandems: no, really… ...</content>
<nick>TG</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://mylife.southdevonhosting.com/pg/blog/lailaida39jj/read/285760/two-days-trip-to-luxor-and-luxor-temple-from-el-go</link>
<time>1313972108</time>
<content>All transfers by air-conditioned modern vehicle class in El Gouna and Luxor - Hotel accommodation in Luxor at 5 * hotel above BB basis. Tour Excludes: - Optional tours - Personal expenses. Two days tumble to Luxor and Luxor temple from El Gouna at vehicle. What To Bring: - Passport legal for 6 months - Comfortable shoes - Cotton clothes in summer - Warm clothes in winter - Sun block - Sunglasses - Hat - Photo/Video Camera Email: nataly@egypttravelhotdeals.com. Website: /&gt; ...</content>
<nick>lailaida39jj</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.crystalvisionswands.com/2011/08/islamic-cairo-travel-package-4-nights-5-days/</link>
<time>1313968576</time>
<content>All sightseeing tours in Cairo are (Private tours) according travel package itinerary – Professional English speaking Egyptologist tour guide – Entrance fees to all sightseeing during Islamic tour in Cairo according itinerary ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://qlife.com.ua/2011/08/blog-post_9744.html</link>
<time>1313967197</time>
<content>natalie-tours.ru. Болгария (Солнечный Берег). Авиаперелет, транcфер, проживание в отеле 5* 7 ночей, питание HВ, медстр. 12 753. www.rv.org.ua. Франция (Лазурный Берег). Авиаперелет, транcфер, проживание в отеле 4* 7 ночей, питание ВВ ...</content>
<nick>e-mail:</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://jimsloire.blogspot.com/2011/08/au-fil-de-aigronne-makes-dinnerla.html</link>
<time>1313962080</time>
<content>Amongst the other people staying there last night was a couple from Tours, who hearing how good La Promenade is, caught the bus that runs from Tours to Tournon Saint-Martin. They had dinner at La Promenade last night and were planning ...</content>
<nick>Jim Budd</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.couponingtodisney.com/2011/08/21/consider-the-lifetime-cost-of-gas-when-purchasing-a-vehicle/</link>
<time>1313960405</time>
<content>Natalie has been visiting Disney World and Disneyland with her son (currently age 5), husband and family for her theme park fun since 1978! Natalie&#39;s passion for Disney has now combined with her Certified Public Accounting license to ...</content>
<nick>Kristin from Couponing to Disney</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://fanmania.info/?p=51050</link>
<time>1314127387</time>
<content>I am doing a report about Armstrong&#39;s incredible life, and I want to know how many Tours de France has he won, because I just can&#39;t find this information.</content>
<nick>Ultimate Fan</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://thingstodo.viator.com/washington-dc/what-do-you-know-about-the-white-house/</link>
<time>1314125761</time>
<content>The public has been able to tour the White House since Jefferson first made it available for this purpose; tours stopped only during wartime. Currently it&#39;s only possible to tour the White House if you submit a request to your own ...</content>
<nick>Viator</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://celebrities-lifenews.com/famous/the-sister-of-lady-gaga-will-undertake-the-costumes-of-a-musical/</link>
<time>1314122429</time>
<content>Natali and Parris met via a designer of cakes – eh Yes!-Tawny Ong, who made a dessert to celebrate the return of Gaga after one of his tours. The creator on cream iced, unconditional of the work of Allison Parris, developed the two ...</content>
<nick>Celebrity</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.travel-guide-tourism.com/travel-news/hurricane-irene-headed-for-united-states.html</link>
<time>1314106035</time>
<content>ToursTravel ideas, Destinations, Cheap Travel, Tourism Guide ... have been altering itineraries in recent days as the storm approaches, with the hub of Puerto Rico already hit. Posted by natalie.blamire@datarsa.com on Aug 23rd, 2011 and filed under Travel News. You can follow any responses to this entry through the RSS 2.0. You can leave a response by filling following comment form or trackback to this entry from your site. You must be logged in to post a comment Login ...</content>
<nick>natalie.blamire@datarsa.com</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.onthegotours.com/blog/2011/08/afternoon-tea-with-whittard-of-chelsea-sponsored-by-on-the-go-tours/</link>
<time>1314097246</time>
<content>On the Go Tours has several itineraries that cater for the tea-lovers out there. For tea-lovers&#39; holidays to India, take a look at the itineraries for Delhi to Darjeeling, Plantations and Hill Stations, Darjeeling High Tea and ...</content>
<nick>Matthew Christensen</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://travel-dream.com.ua/turoperator-natali-turs-vyshel-na-ukrainskij-rynok</link>
<time>1314095258</time>
<content>Ведущий российский туроператор &quot;Натали Турс&quot; объявил о начале работы в Украине. Планируемый объем инвестиций в украинский рынок в 2011 году составит около 1 млн.</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.8newsnow.com/story/15307337/kims-russia-trip-focusing-on-energy-issue</link>
<time>1314094560</time>
<content>By HYUNG-JIN KIM and NATALIYA VASILYEVA Associated Press. MOSCOW (AP) - North Korean leader Kim Jong Il on Tuesday toured around the world&#39;s largest freshwater lake in eastern Siberia and visited an aircraft factory, leaving his armored ...</content>
<nick>неизвестен</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.golfaid.com/2011/08/23/long-putters-surge-in-popularity</link>
<time>1314105860</time>
<content>What&#39;s responsible for the surge in popularity of the long putter on professional golf tours? Why are so many PGA and now LPGA Tour golfers using the belly and.</content>
<nick>WalterLis</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://besthoteldiscounts.com/?p=4107</link>
<time>1314105602</time>
<content>Day 4: Nile Cruise: Kom Ombo – Edfu Tours Early morning sail to Kom Ombo where you will see unique Kom Ombo Temple, because in fact it a double temple built in Greco-Roman period and dedicated to Sobek and Horus. ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://besthoteldiscounts.com/?p=4093</link>
<time>1314105181</time>
<content>All sightseeing tours in Cairo are (Private tours) according tour itinerary – Entrance fees to all sites according tour itinerary – Lunch meals during tours as per itinerary – All taxes &amp; services charges. Travel Package Excludes: ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://besthoteldiscounts.com/?p=4089</link>
<time>1314105063</time>
<content>Day # 2) Sharm El Sheikh / Giza Sightseeing Tours Breakfast at your hotel in Sharm El Sheikh then you will be transferred to Sharm El Sheikh airport to fly to Cairo, where you will be met and assisted and then you will be accompanied by ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.travel-guide-tourism.com/travel-news/network-rail-route-improvement-work-means-changes-to-virgin-trains%E2%80%99-services.html</link>
<time>1314104402</time>
<content>ToursTravel ideas, Destinations, Cheap Travel, Tourism Guide ... Network Rail route improvement work means changes to Virgin Trains&#39; services at 2011 August Bank Holiday weekend. Posted by natalie.blamire@datarsa.com on Aug 23rd, 2011 and filed under Travel News. You can follow any responses to this entry through the RSS 2.0. You can leave a response by filling following comment form or trackback to this entry from your site. You must be logged in to post a comment Login ...</content>
<nick>natalie.blamire@datarsa.com</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.travel-guide-tourism.com/travel-news/kate-winslet-escapes-fire-on-branson%E2%80%99s-necker-island.html</link>
<time>1314102090</time>
<content>ToursTravel ideas, Destinations, Cheap Travel, Tourism Guide ... being struck by lightning during a tropical storm. As many as 20 guests were evacuated following the incident. Posted by natalie.blamire@datarsa.com on Aug 23rd, 2011 and filed under Travel News. You can follow any responses to this entry through the RSS 2.0. You can leave a response by filling following comment form or trackback to this entry from your site. You must be logged in to post a comment Login ...</content>
<nick>natalie.blamire@datarsa.com</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.travel-guide-tourism.com/travel-news/europcar-opens-new-branch-in-omagh.html</link>
<time>1314100843</time>
<content>ToursTravel ideas, Destinations, Cheap Travel, Tourism Guide ... car hire more accessible than ever for customers in Northern Ireland, with the opening of a new station in Omagh. Posted by natalie.blamire@datarsa.com on Aug 23rd, 2011 and filed under Travel News. You can follow any responses to this entry through the RSS 2.0. You can leave a response by filling following comment form or trackback to this entry from your site. You must be logged in to post a comment Login ...</content>
<nick>natalie.blamire@datarsa.com</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://backofthebookreviews.com/2011/08/paradise-21-blog-tour-interview/</link>
<time>1314100808</time>
<content>We are honoured to be joined today by Aubrie Dionne, thanks to Bewitching Blog Tours. We wanted to do this one a little differently so we have conducted a spotlight style interview. Also one lucky winner will receive a copy of her ...</content>
<nick>Ashley</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://musicmattersblog.com/2011/08/23/win-a-free-month-of-full-access-to-theta-music-trainer/</link>
<time>1314097210</time>
<content>Filed under: Contests,On-line Resources,Resource Reviews,Technology Tips — natalie @ 6:00 am. Don&#39;t you love it when site developers are committed to continually improving their resources and adding value to their customers? ... Piano Camp Ideas · Practice Incentives · Questions for Discussion · Random · Recital Ideas · Repertoire Suggestions · Resource Reviews · Rhythm Blocks · Scale Blocks · Store · Student Surveys · Studio Ideas · Studio Tours · Teaching Ideas ...</content>
<nick>natalie</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://livegolfvideos.com/holmes-to-have-brain-surgery-miss-3-months/</link>
<time>1314096571</time>
<content>Ai Miyazato Videos · Anna Rawson Videos · Cristie Kerr Videos · Natalie Gulbis Videos · Yani Tseng Videos · Jim Furyk Videos · Lee Westwood Videos · Luke Donald Videos · Martin Kaymer Videos · Moe Norman · Padraig Harrington · Paul Casey Videos ... Golf.com: Tours &amp; News. From Live Golf Videos/Golf News, post Holmes to have brain surgery, miss 3 months. Post Footer automatically generated by wp-posturl plugin for wordpress. VN:F [1.9.10_1130]. please wait. ...</content>
<nick>Live Golf Videos</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://besthoteldiscounts.com/?p=3744</link>
<time>1314094742</time>
<content>Day # 2) Sharm El Sheikh / Giza Sightseeing Tours Breakfast at your hotel in Sharm El Sheikh then you will be transferred to Sharm El Sheikh airport to fly to Cairo, where you will be met and assisted and then you will be accompanied by ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://besthoteldiscounts.com/?p=3703</link>
<time>1314093542</time>
<content>All sightseeing tours in Cairo are (Private tours) according itinerary – Entrance fees to all sites according Travel Package itinerary – Lunch meals during tours as per itinerary – All taxes &amp; services charges ... can be done online by Credit card, Visa and Master or bank transfer 75% balance will required in arrival in Egypt and can be paid by credit cards or cash. Email: nataly@egypttravelhotdeals.com. Website: www.egypttravelhotdeals.com. Article from articlesbase.com ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://jssnews.com/2011/08/23/egypte-vers-une-interdiction-du-bikini-sur-les-plages/</link>
<time>1314091719</time>
<content>Voilà une réunion qui devrait ravir les tours operators… Mais, quand on sait que pour quelques dollars, les Islamistes ferment bien vite leurs yeux sur un bon verre de whisky et quelques “chiennes et cochonnes” d&#39;infidèles occidentales en ..... Advietov : nos modèles se nomment Gal Gadot, Natalie Herschlag (Portman), Mia Kirshner, Bar Rafaeli et tant d&#39;autres… Désolé pour toi : ce sont de belles et de vraies Juives. Jalouse va ! :lol: Signaler ce commentaire au webmaster ...</content>
<nick>JSS</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://fanmania.info/?p=50420</link>
<time>1314085853</time>
<content>Yes–MIchael had the top selling ALBUM ever and his tours did AMAZING like Madonna&#39;s. BUT—–Madonna has the top tour ever for a solo artist and is the top selling female—thats what I meant. So I am correct. Thanks. ...</content>
<nick>Ultimate Fan</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.wbez.org/story/emanuel-takes-chicagos-food-deserts-90776</link>
<time>1314079842</time>
<content>(WBEZ/Natalie Moore). Food desert expert Mari Gallagher tours a farmers market in Chicago&#39;s Pullman neighborhood. Chicago mayor Rahm Emanuel&#39;s 100th day in office is approaching, and we&#39;re taking stock of his progress. ...</content>
<nick>неизвестен</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.fireworkspr.com.au/?p=401</link>
<time>1314079669</time>
<content>Howard Park Operations Manager, Natalie Burch, said that it was interesting to note the different strengths and personalities at each of the South Australian wineries that were visited. ... The group enjoyed tours and tastings at their South Australian AFFW member&#39;s vineyards, including Taylors, Jim Barry Wines, Henschke, Yalumba and d&#39;Arenberg. Some of the highlights of the trip included a stunning lunch at Taylors in the St Andrews building of the property. ...</content>
<nick>Kathy Lane</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://deceiver.com/2011/08/23/dov-charney-loves-teenagers/</link>
<time>1314077296</time>
<content>Top Ten Deceivers. Snooki · Natalie Portman · Jessica Biel · Sesame Street · Gwyneth Paltrow · Jon Stewart · Kelly Osbourne · PETA · LeAnn Rimes · Scarlett Johansson ... Obama Tours Country in Canadian-Made Van, Vows to Put Americans to Work · Warren Buffett Doesn&#39;t Want the Tax Breaks He Takes · Suicide Takes a Spotlight to the Real Housewives Franchise · A&amp;F Will Pay The “Situation” to Stop Wearing Their Clothes · Octomom Plays Armchair Psychologist With Casey Anthony ...</content>
<nick>Pastafarian</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.timezeroart.com/music/critiques-of-new-pop-countrybeat-jazz-and-classical-music-releases/</link>
<time>1314076600</time>
<content>Contributing to the sumptuous settings of producer Todd Barkan are tenor saxophonist Harry Allen, pianist John di Martino, and trumpeter Terell Stafford of Temple&#39;s jazz faculty. DONIZETTI &amp;quotLucia di Lammermoor&amp;quot Natalie Dessay, ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.sinemacenter.com/soguk-dag-izle/</link>
<time>1314076190</time>
<content>-Soğuk Dağ / Cold Mountain 2004 ABD,İngiltere,Romanya,İtalya / TÜRKÇE DUBLAJ-IMDB Puanı: 7.3/10. Tür: Dram, Romantik, Savaş Yönetmen: Anthony Minghella Müzik: Gabriel Yared Süre: 2 saat 35 dk. Oyuncular: Natalie Portman, Nicole Kidman, ...</content>
<nick>sinema</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://tlcbooktours.com/2011/08/james-martin-author-of-between-heaven-and-mirth-on-tour-october-2011/</link>
<time>1314075843</time>
<content>Before entering the Jesuits, he graduated from the Wharton School of Business and worked with General Electric for six years. You can connect with Rev. Martin by following his blog and liking him on Facebook. Categories: blog tours ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.travel-guide-tourism.com/travel-news/ihg-announces-development-team-changes-in-the-americas-region.html</link>
<time>1314075658</time>
<content>ToursTravel ideas, Destinations, Cheap Travel, Tourism Guide ... allowing IHG to leverage internal talent, maintain brand-centric structure and focus on owner relations. Posted by natalie.blamire@datarsa.com on Aug 23rd, 2011 and filed under Travel News. You can follow any responses to this entry through the RSS 2.0. You can leave a response by filling following comment form or trackback to this entry from your site. You must be logged in to post a comment Login ...</content>
<nick>natalie.blamire@datarsa.com</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.alldailydeals.ca/go/a2vc</link>
<time>1314075601</time>
<content>-Natalie, Georgetown. &quot;I wanted to email and say what a great time we had with our WagJag deal at Snow Valley yesterday. It was great to try out a new ski hill and the deal was wonderful. I tracked down the person who works at Snow Valley in Promotions and ... Cannot wait to see how well the scenic tours will do!&quot; -Mike Duncan, Owner, Prestige Sportfishing. &quot;So far the WagJag people seem to be very happy with us. Most of them have returned as new patients so I am stoked!&quot; ...</content>
<nick>неизвестен</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.temptalia.com/have-you-ever-had-your-makeup-done-by-a-professional</link>
<time>1314075601</time>
<content>Twice, I had an artist from Laura Mercier (he does circuit tours of the Laura Mercier counters around my area) do my makeup. He was absolutely phenomonal and on a completely different plane than the other SAs at the local counters. .... Natalie says: August 23, 2011 at 7:10 am. I have, several times for a few different occasions like prom, graduation and some weddings. I just do it when I feel I either need it to be extra perfect, or I won&#39;t have time to do it how I want ...</content>
<nick>Christine</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.alldailydeals.ca/go/3asA</link>
<time>1314075601</time>
<content>-Natalie, Georgetown. &quot;This past weekend my family and I used up two different WagJag offers in the Niagara Region (greenhouse and a bar and grill) and I must say it was so worth it!!! We had such a great time and got a great value for our ... Unreal results! I am so impressed with WagJag that I would definitely promote Prestige through it again! Cannot wait to see how well the scenic tours will do!&quot; -Mike Duncan, Owner, Prestige Sportfishing. What Merchants are Saying ...</content>
<nick>неизвестен</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.cuscomania.com/2011/08/cuscomania/analisis-de-la-pelicula-%E2%80%9Csearch-for-el-dorado-%E2%80%9D-con-shane-west/</link>
<time>1314071204</time>
<content>Esta producción está protagonizada por los actores Shane West, Luke Goss, Natalie Martínez, Elden Henson, Julio Mechoso y producida por Luis Llosa; pero tambien veremos a algunos actores peruano entre ellos Vanessa Saba, Giovanni Ciccia ...</content>
<nick>Diego Amachi</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.wave3.com/story/15307337/kims-russia-trip-focusing-on-energy-issue</link>
<time>1314071160</time>
<content>WAVE 3 News - Louisville, KentuckyKim tours Baikal ahead of summit with Medvedev. Member Center: Create Account|; Log In; Manage Account|; Log Out. SITE SEARCH WEB SEARCH BY Google .... By HYUNG-JIN KIM and NATALIYA VASILYEVA Associated Press. MOSCOW (AP) - North Korean leader Kim Jong Il on Tuesday toured around the world&#39;s largest freshwater lake in eastern Siberia and visited an aircraft factory, leaving his armored train en route to meet with Russian President Dmitry ...</content>
<nick>неизвестен</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://the-vampirediaries.com/2011/08/22/the-vampire-diaries-season-3-the-birthday-3x01-hq-episode-stills/</link>
<time>1314068399</time>
<content>August 22nd, 2011 | Author: Natalie. Added 9 HQ stills from “The Birthday” which is The Vampire Diaries&#39;s Season 3 Premiere episode. The series premieres on the CW on September 15th. ...</content>
<nick>Natalie</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.appleboxfilmmakers.com/multiple-award-winning-patriotic-anti-war-film-will-premiere-at-prestigious-film-festival-in-new-york/</link>
<time>1314064805</time>
<content>He&#39;s toured with Ella Fitzgerald, Fran Sinatra, etc., etc. and tours with Tony Bennett today. Also solo Guitarist and composer John Chiodini, who has recorded and toured with Peggy Lee, Natalie Cole, Nina Simone, Barbara Streisand and ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://pagosasprings.com/16301/</link>
<time>1314063090</time>
<content>Ask The Editor · Jim Smith Realty · MLS Property Search · Interactive Map Search · Hot Sheet · Virtual Tours · Property Data/Tax Info · Pagosa Real Estate Magazine · Old Articles · Submit Your Event ...</content>
<nick>normvance</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://stop-right-there.com/36582/travelling-light-whats-inside-your-backpack/</link>
<time>1314061574</time>
<content>I especially prefer that airport terminal scene where he was instructing the young and excited Natalie Keener, about how packing light with just the necessities, can save you a great deal of time and energy. This is just what most people, specifically those who are not likely the avid traveler, lose out when getting last minute vacation or even planned tours. They take with them plenty of things, with the concern in mind that they could need it along the way. ...</content>
<nick>garrymadison</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.cheapcruisesjamaica.com/dj-ikp-the-rum-punch-mix-hiphopthugz-com-mixtapes-free/</link>
<time>1314060906</time>
<content>Mavado- So Special 9. Serani- No Games ... 61. Alison Hinds- Baddest Wine 62. Skinny Fabolous- 6.30 63. Lil Rick- Work 64. Enur Ft. Beenie Man &amp; Natalie- Whine 65. Benjai- Wine To The Side 66. No Doubt- Underneath It All 67.</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.couponingtodisney.com/2011/08/22/extra-cash-earn-gift-cards-from-my-points/</link>
<time>1314059442</time>
<content>13 Natalie May 22, 2010 at 5:21 pm. I&#39;ve been with MyPoints for 1 year and was afraid to download the toolbar fearing a virus. Has anyone had trouble with that? Reply. 14 amy August 23, 2011 at 5:52 am ...</content>
<nick>Kristin from Couponing to Disney</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://babycareblog.org/babys/</link>
<time>1314057798</time>
<content>After all, in the two months since giving birth to her son Aleph, Natalie Portman has been keeping an extremely low profile—a decision the Oscar winner hinted at just prior to the baby&#39;s arrival. ... going to be 60 years old next summer, having enjoyed success beyond his wildest dreams through the years -- scoring No. 1 singles, playing arena tours, being a member of Ringo Starr&#39;s All-Star band -- yet it has taken until now for John Waite to finally find some real peace. ...</content>
<nick>Anders Utkilen</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://thingstodo.viator.com/montreal/33/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=33</link>
<time>1314054648</time>
<content>And even if you can&#39;t tell the difference – just don&#39;t tell either of them that they sound the same! -Natalie Grant. Planning a trip? Browse Viator&#39;s Montreal tours &amp; things to do, Montreal attractions, and Montreal travel ...</content>
<nick>Viator</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://marcandrewsblog.blogspot.com/2011/08/moby-interview.html</link>
<time>1314054300</time>
<content>[Laughs] Part of it is my interest in going to places I&#39;ve never been to before and part of it is the nature of festival tours. In Australia they have the decency to route them one after the other in a logical way, but in Europe you have Tuesday in .... You recently did an interview with gay writer/director Stephen Dalton where you talked about your gay experiences, drug taking days and dating Natalie Portman! Stephen Dalton and I have a long strange history [laughs]. ...</content>
<nick>Marc Andrews (aka marc-e-marc)</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
