<post>
<link>http://undergroundsportsnetwork.net/site/2011/08/22/watch-videoshaq-slapped-by-betty-white-after-funny-marriage-proposal/</link>
<time>1314040812</time>
<content>Shaquille O&#39;Neal is retired from the NBA, but it appears he will be doing his own stunts as he keeps in tough with the world via videos he posts on Twitter. Here, Shaq takes a shot from an angry Betty White. Time for another Snickers, ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.debbieschlussel.com/41099/huh-israel-apologizes-this-is-what-peace-w-palestinian-muslims-looks-like/</link>
<time>1314040362</time>
<content>Nothin&#39; (other than snickers). In fact, the Egyptians won&#39;t be nicer and are already saying the apology is “not enough.” Egypt won&#39;t stop more HAMAS and Fatah and Al-Qaeda terrorists from attacking Israel from the Sinai and entering ...</content>
<nick>Debbie</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://ramcsays.wordpress.com/2011/08/22/dhada-devastating-worthless-movie/</link>
<time>1314039412</time>
<content>Sense less comedy “wtf he is trying to show “ A tiger eating snickers and getting away…talking to tiger. It was seriously devastating watching this movie. Spending 50/- for this movie…need to think , as you may get something worthful ...</content>
<nick>ramcsays</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://roam365.wordpress.com/2011/08/22/zw/</link>
<time>1314039198</time>
<content>To highlight tis imeras mou omos itan pou emirastikame mia snickers me ton PC san ekarterousame e3w sta e3wterika iatreia. Oulloi oi as8eneis pou eka8ountan jiame en kardiopa8eis me K kefalaio. Je lalw tou PC &#39; re na men tin fame dame ...</content>
<nick>RoAm</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://childrensmovies.bestordernow.com/kids-react-to-viral-videos-1-double-rainbow-obama-fail-twin-rabbits-snickers-halloween/</link>
<time>1314037200</time>
<content>TAGS: thefinebros the fine brothers benny rafi bros kids react viral videos kids say the darndest things cute kids children funny words video double rainbow 2 two bunnies cups creepy snickers halloween commercial obama podium fail cute ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://arttoattractingyourman.com/mr-t-snickers-commercial/</link>
<time>1314033182</time>
<content>KaliMuscle says: August 22, 2011 at 7:15 pm (UTC 0). Reply. MR.T DON&#39;T HAVE NOTHING ON KALI MUSCLE! CHECK OUT SNICKERS COMMERCIAL (BODYBUILDER IN DRESS). masterDevis says: August 22, 2011 at 7:30 pm (UTC 0) ...</content>
<nick>tina</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://modelfitchallenge.wordpress.com/2011/08/22/day-33-mfit-challenge/</link>
<time>1314032690</time>
<content>But fingers crossed it will be a great event. Confessions: Pulled pork is my true love. I&#39;m not a meat person boy does pulled pork turn me on! I also had some ice cream. The snickers bar treats really do make you scream. ...</content>
<nick>jesgut</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://hitomoneya.com/?p=2250</link>
<time>1314030911</time>
<content>EMINEM (оптом или в розницу) – одна штука; BRUNO MARS (не путать со SNICKERS или BOUNTY) – полкило. Предварительно посолить и дать слезам горючим стечь в отдельную посуду. далеко не убирайте – они понадобятся для того, чтобы сдобрить ...</content>
<nick>Smirnoff</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://a8lumenpsychic.com/bestprice-blanco-440080-performa-silgranit-ii-single-bowl-sink-biscuit/</link>
<time>1314037021</time>
<content>For Sale Snickers Minis 24 Pack · OrderNow Jako for Men by Karl Lagerfeld 4.2 oz EDT Spray Tester · Look Brandt Narcotics Safe, Double Door, 24 x 16 x 8 · OrderNow Iranian Sevruga 000 Caviar 5.5 oz 157 g (Free Overnight Shipping!) ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://latinwave.cl/2011/08/el-sueco-sven-thorgren-se-queda-con-el-%E2%80%9Cbillabong-big-air-nocturno%E2%80%9D/</link>
<time>1314034793</time>
<content>Con gran marco de público culminó el primero campeonato de snowboard nocturno de esta temporada, nos referimos al “Billabong Big Air Nocturno” by Snickers, presentado por HP y Windows 7. Evento que premió con el trofeo del primer lugar ...</content>
<nick>Fercata19</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.surfing-network.net/blog/view/id_90384</link>
<time>1314033874</time>
<content>A Snickers bar is full of chocolate but it also is jam packed with peanuts and caramel so you have to eat your way around the candy bar to get your dose of pure chocolate. Thankfully, there are gourmet chocolates available to fulfill ...</content>
<nick>неизвестен</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://yougabsports.com/pt/Vacating-Titles-Who-does-this-really-serve/blog.htm</link>
<time>1314033672</time>
<content>Sure he has something of value, he is chagrined when Rick snickers in a kind of hiss and offers 5 bucks!! Even Chumley knows the deal on this one. Reggie Bush was on his own TV set. Let&#39;s Make A Deal. The booster probably assured the ...</content>
<nick>неизвестен</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.pangeareptile.com/forums/showthread.php?t=54114</link>
<time>1314033577</time>
<content>Thread, Thread Starter, Forum, Replies, Last Post. Crestie questions, Snickers, CRESTED GECKOS, 32, 10-13-2010 12:10 PM. Crestie gone wild... seeking help through the aftermath, Boo, CRESTED GECKOS, 16, 12-11-2009 07:29 PM ...</content>
<nick>unluckytoe</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://animefilms.net/3d-live-video-display/</link>
<time>1314031993</time>
<content>Created by TBWAChiatDay for Snickers, it is not 3d in the sense that we all may think… like the movies where you wear glasses and things zoom out at you. It is 3D in the sense that when you move, your perspective changes and the image ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.thisconfettilife.com/2011/08/packing-light/</link>
<time>1314030182</time>
<content>The last time I travelled internationally, I ended up in the Yucatan with just a Snickers bar, an issue of Vanity Fair, and two safety pins, which is why on my next international vacation, I&#39;m carrying on. I bought a carry-on approved ...</content>
<nick>Janet</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.addictedtosaving.com/2011/08/22/publix-yellow-advantage-flyer-82011-9911/</link>
<time>1314029786</time>
<content>Snickers or Twix ice cream bars, 6 ct, or Snickers Minis ice cream bars, 12 ct, 2 for $6.00. Mott&#39;s or Hawaiian Punch fruit snacks, 10 pk, 9 oz, 2 for $3.00. Ken&#39;s dressing, 9 oz, 2 for $2.00. -$1/1 Ken&#39;s Dressing 8/14/2011 SS Insert ...</content>
<nick>liza@addictedtosaving.com (Liza Ford)</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.ad3s.com/snickers-peanut-butter-squared-focus-group.html</link>
<time>1314029240</time>
<content>No matter who you are, if you like peanut butter and chocolate, you&#39;ll love peanut butter and Snickers. Check out our new commercial.</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.designcot.com/2011/08/5-top-stunner-at-2011-pebble-beach-auction/</link>
<time>1314028978</time>
<content>It&#39;s also a cunning Snickers shade of brown, which makes it empirically superior to anything of its era or of this one, not to mention delicious. Dig the original seats: we wish every Camaro and Mustang came with buckets ribbed like ...</content>
<nick>designcot</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.southbayrantsnraves.com/wordpress/?p=2475</link>
<time>1314028827</time>
<content>It helped that the recipe called for Snickers, my favorite candy. The whole process was actually quick and painless. Personally, I think it could be sweeter. I&#39;ll add more Snickers… and then take an extra couple of laps at the rink. ...</content>
<nick>southbayrantsnraves</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://martesnickers.wordpress.com/2011/08/22/21-augustus-2011/</link>
<time>1314028810</time>
<content>Geplaatst op 22 augustus 2011 door Marte Snickers| Plaats een reactie. Ik ben back in Belgium! Het was tof, maar zo anders zonder pap ;s Maarja, kheb me geamuseerd &amp; dat is het belangrijkste, toch? Het was er echt schitterend weer. ...</content>
<nick>Marte Snickers</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://kerganedwards-stout.com/festive-beaver/</link>
<time>1314027923</time>
<content>One dumb-witted boy, Shawn “Snickers” O&#39;Toole, mocked Rusty, suggesting that Rusty was just looking for an excuse to don a dress. Rusty threw Snickers his best diva glare, then went on outlining his plans. As Little Rusty continued, ...</content>
<nick>Kergan Edwards-Stout</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.racingwisconsin.com/story.asp?aid=4571</link>
<time>1314027922</time>
<content>Dustin Boney worked his Snickers-sponsored mount past Ruter at the same time, got by Anderson on lap 11 and began to reel in Gustin as the leader reached lapped traffic with 17 laps complete. The caution flag waved at the halfway point, ...</content>
<nick>неизвестен</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://chinaloj.livejournal.com/104057.html</link>
<time>1314027183</time>
<content>But we&#39;re a little concerned about these 14-year-olds and their Facebook petition to replace Bob Costas with Justin Bieber, and Al Michaels with a really cute guinea pig named Snickers. ryan seacrest, ed asner, vince lombardi, ...</content>
<nick>chinaloj</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.cookthatbook.com/2011/08/22/muffin-monday-snickers-peanut-butter-muffins/</link>
<time>1314023433</time>
<content>Snickers Bars: Brand name candy bar consisting of peanut nougat topped with roasted peanuts and caramel, and covered in milk chocolate. Nigella Lawson: English food writer famed for her (ahem) sensual approach to food. ...</content>
<nick>Stay-At-Home-Chef</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://wldy-wjbl.com/news/?p=3468</link>
<time>1314023171</time>
<content>Dustin Boney worked his Snickers-sponsored mount past Ruter at the same time, got by Anderson on lap 11 and began to reel in Gustin as the leader reached lapped traffic with 17 laps complete. The caution flag waved at the halfway point, ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://thelastbrokenhome.com/2011/08/22/quick-tlbh-news/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=quick-tlbh-news</link>
<time>1314022261</time>
<content>... and worked on some other endeavors which will be of help to me, and thus the site. Hopefully you stuck around. Hopefully you&#39;ll stick around. Hopefully I&#39;ll win a lifetime supply of snickers bars for some reason. That&#39;d be sweet. ...</content>
<nick>Adam Alvarado</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://cjromb.com/2011/08/22/first-day/</link>
<time>1314021618</time>
<content>You pack their nutritious lunch or give them money, hoping they don&#39;t spend it on chips, snickers and soda. You arrange after school care hoping they have fun and get their homework done, somehow at the same time. ...</content>
<nick>cjromb</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://geology.com/news/2011/gold-in-newfoundland.shtml</link>
<time>1314021397</time>
<content>Now you can get a Snickers bar and then buy a bar... Gold as a Currency Standard November 9, 2010 | Reuters UK A Reuters article traces the use of gold as a currency standard.... Another Gold Price Record: $1258.38 ...</content>
<nick>Geology.com</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://vivalamarla.com/2011/08/adventures-in-borrowing/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=adventures-in-borrowing</link>
<time>1314021036</time>
<content>Snickers the cat - our female kitty, overly playful &amp; cute as a kitten (pun intended) Pepper the cat - Snickers&#39; male play-mate, handsome, laid-back, &amp; wishes he were an outdoor kitty (but deep-down inside, he&#39;s really a scaredy cat) ...</content>
<nick>Marla</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://ethiomusicians.com/blog/view/id_72950</link>
<time>1314020656</time>
<content>Sneakers -- Hand techniques handbags tend to be totally different from your current typical snickers along with rubber-soled handbags. Boxing handbags are lighter in weight, leather-based soled and gives exceptional ankle support. ...</content>
<nick>неизвестен</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.stylemagazine.com/america-loves-betty-white-best/</link>
<time>1314018616</time>
<content>Last year, White won an Emmy for her “Saturday Night Live” hosting gig, and the actress has recently appeared in Snickers commercials and TV shows like “Community” and “Hot in Cleveland.” And you&#39;ll be seeing more of White this fall; ...</content>
<nick>CNN News Wire</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://sallygary.wordpress.com/2011/08/22/a-tip-for-the-first-day-of-school/</link>
<time>1314018137</time>
<content>Snickers all around. “Butt.” Full-blown nervous laughter, followed by “Uuummmm!” and hands being clasped over mouths. It&#39;s 1967, remember. More guesses, followed by a loving “nooo,” or “not quite.” I raised my hand slowly from the back ...</content>
<nick>sallygary</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.abqjournalfit.com/2011/08/22/healthy-vending-machines-dispense-with-junk-food/</link>
<time>1314017451</time>
<content>“Look, I eat Snickers bars,” he said. “But there are so many other interesting products that the public never sees. Believe it or not, I like rice milk now. And I never would have tried it otherwise.” Carpenter knows healthy vending ...</content>
<nick>The Associated Press</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.babyblogs.info/kids/yes-kandee-johnson-is-pregnant-update-video.html</link>
<time>1314016270</time>
<content>*snickers. CassieAnnaCary Says: 八月 22nd, 2011 at 23:07:45. @HelloKitty261000 Its a Glory Hole baby. CassieAnnaCary Says: 八月 22nd, 2011 at 23:30:41. @xolozziibaybee hey…is your tongue attached to Kandee&#39;s ass? ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://ryjik-donya.livejournal.com/145169.html</link>
<time>1314016056</time>
<content>На улице солнце. Надо расчесаться. Джинсы. Кроссовки. Смс напишу малявке одной, пойдем гулять. Не могу расчесаться. Руки. Голова. Слезы. Сникерс купить. Люблю сникерс. И мороженое. Магазин на улице. Расчесаться надо. Не могу. ...</content>
<nick>ryjik_donya</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://natureshealthysolutions.com/obamas-nutrition-bill-gaffe-of-the-week/</link>
<time>1314015557</time>
<content>There&#39;s a sixth-grader, &#39;Eddie&#39;, who sells Snickers and Butterfingers for .50 out of his backpack; and he does a good business. I pawned my Dad&#39;s electric drill for , so I&#39;m good for the week.” “And what about dinner?” ...</content>
<nick>Tom Brighten</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.internetappdeveloper.com/?p=1055&utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=minneapolis-web-design-agency-%25e2%2580%2593-internet-exposure-%25e2%2580%2593-launches-a-free-minnesota</link>
<time>1314015193</time>
<content>Note: Fair Shake, a Minnesota State Fair iPhone app, does not cure Spamburger-induced hysteria or deep-fried Snickers-psychosis. Minneapolis, MN (PRWEB) August 22, 2011. Internet Exposure, a Minneapolis web design agency, ...</content>
<nick>Moderator</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://sundayyoga.com/do-i-exercise-too-much.html</link>
<time>1314014475</time>
<content>My body won&#39;t digest too much sugar and certain types of candy (snickers, twix, crunch, etc.). Cheese makes me sick. I have a serious allergic reactions to some types of peppers. I eat everything I can but I can&#39;t gain weight. ...</content>
<nick>неизвестен</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.myipadblogs.com/ipad-2-smart-covers/</link>
<time>1314014142</time>
<content>i Just left the apple store holding 1. it was beyond my imagination better than what i thought best product ing the world better than a snickers bar. the ipad 2 is so easy to use and so much fun i want 1 sooooooo bad. hariupad007 says: ...</content>
<nick>Mark</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.pula-symp.com/developing-historical-past-benefits-of-using-sentence-eyeglass-frames-to-build-historical-past-knowledge/</link>
<time>1314013618</time>
<content>My business is such as this _____(Snickers pub), mainly because My business is _____ (crazy). My business is such as this _____(Matchbox Porsche), mainly because My business is _____ (small, and quickly). ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.rudetrude.com/health-fitness/foot-health/acyclovir-dosage/</link>
<time>1314013611</time>
<content>I notice the Snickers guy who sings the “waterfall of caramel” also contained by valtrex commercial? everyone?added. I own herpes and appreciate be experiencing numerous breakouts although taking valtrex over the second year. ...</content>
<nick>alphonseco33</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://healthyshe.com/acyclovir-dosage</link>
<time>1314013599</time>
<content>I notice the Snickers guy who sings the “waterfall of caramel” also contained by valtrex commercial? everyone?extra. I own herpes and take pleasure in be experiencing many breakouts even though taking valtrex over the second year. ...</content>
<nick>alphonseco33</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://atworkcom.com/side-effects-of-acyclovir/</link>
<time>1314013580</time>
<content>I notice the Snickers guy who sings the “waterfall of caramel” also contained by valtrex commercial? anyone?extra. I own herpes and get pleasure from be experiencing several breakouts while taking valtrex over the second year. ...</content>
<nick>alphonseco33</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://movemoon.livejournal.com/61031.html</link>
<time>1314012342</time>
<content>Оригинал взят у ibigdan в Шоколадки в разрезе Твикс Сникерс Сникерс баттер Марс Кит Кат Кит Кат белый шоколад Кит кат большой Hershey&#39;s - Air Delight Тоблерон Буэно Виспа …</content>
<nick>movemoon</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://gamesorange.ru/2011/08/22/dune-rainbow-to-the-stars/</link>
<time>1314011534</time>
<content>jshulz2115 : 22.08.2011 в 12:23 пп. DUDE, this music makes me so happy. Im naked right now masterbating to Boku no Pico (mute). blasting this happy hardcore and eating a king size snickers. and yes im very overweight. ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.spinsucks.com/communication/public-relations-for-sharks/</link>
<time>1314010818</time>
<content>Ali Mac 52 pts. Vending machines?! Can&#39;t believe those poor sharks get such a bad rap, while our 3pm snack attack can cause some serious damage. Damn you, Snickers bar! ;). share flag. spam; offensive; disagree; off topic ...</content>
<nick>Gini Dietrich</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.grrlpowercomic.com/archives/317</link>
<time>1314010800</time>
<content>*snickers*. On another note, have several containers with cloth straps, they seem to have removable / adjustable connections to the container so you can adjust for peak carrying comfort.. I do suppose what make Sydney sooooo funny is ...</content>
<nick>DaveB</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://virtualhow2.com/articles/2011/08/22/acyclovir-side-effects/</link>
<time>1314010001</time>
<content>I notice the Snickers guy who sings the “waterfall of caramel” also contained by valtrex commercial? everyone?extra. I own herpes and take pleasure in be experiencing many breakouts even though taking valtrex over the second year. ...</content>
<nick>alphonseco33</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://vadimb.livejournal.com/1352760.html</link>
<time>1314009116</time>
<content>Мы заслужили к себе такое отношение потому, что променяли империю на сникерс. Как только этнос сбрасывает с себя тяжелую ношу ответственности за мир и порядок в империи, он становится козлом отпущения, виноватым за все и перед всеми. ...</content>
<nick>vadimb</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://wasabi.lizi.pl/374/wysmienite-ciasto-snikers/</link>
<time>1314009087</time>
<content>Ciasto snickers to ciasto jakie zwala z nóg zarówno osobę która je upiekła jak i również wszystkich gości. Raj dla naszego podniebienia! Sprawdź które ciasta uda Ci się upiec dla swoich najbliższych! Po pokryciu świeżych orzechów ...</content>
<nick>неизвестен</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://ide-i.livejournal.com/328247.html</link>
<time>1314007815</time>
<content>Оригинал взят у ibigdan в Шоколадки в разрезе Твикс Сникерс Сникерс баттер Марс Кит Кат Кит Кат белый шоколад Кит кат большой Hershey&#39;s - Air Delight Тоблерон Буэно Виспа М&amp;Ms…</content>
<nick>ide_i</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://k8edid.wordpress.com/2011/08/22/its-in-his-kiss/</link>
<time>1314007673</time>
<content>Sure he buys himself a couple extra lottery tickets, a 20 ounce and 3 Snickers bars while he&#39;s there (and takes it out of your spending money). That&#39;s love. And most importantly, doesn&#39;t he keep your dog&#39;s poop cleaned up in the yard? ...</content>
<nick>k8edid</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://busy-at-home.com/blog/hello-snickers-bars-my-august-secret-recipe-club-entry-2/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=hello-snickers-bars-my-august-secret-recipe-club-entry-2</link>
<time>1314007255</time>
<content>Chocolatey, caramely, gooey, chewy goodness with the wonderful texture contrast of crunchy peanuts. Yum! You&#39;ll love this easy, peasy recipe!</content>
<nick>Glenda Embree</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://pickyeatingrd.com/2011/08/wine-tasting-date-night/</link>
<time>1314007222</time>
<content>I grabbed a Snickers cheesecake pop and E had a Bailey&#39;s truffle. He said his was a little rich but mine.was.perfect. We both had such a great time talking, eating, and being pretend winos. Until next time date night..until next time… ...</content>
<nick>Allie</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://tinepoverish.livejournal.com/1872430.html</link>
<time>1314007183</time>
<content>Originally published at Лучшие цитаты Рунета . You can comment here or there . Твикс Сникерс Сникерс баттер Марс Кит Кат Кит Кат белый шоколад Кит кат большой Hershey&#39;s – Air Delight Тоблерон …</content>
<nick>tinepoverish</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://insomniousnights.wordpress.com/2011/08/22/paramore-in-singapore-21st-august-2011/</link>
<time>1314006951</time>
<content>About jannahward. ǰɐɴɴɐʜʓ☮/. Libran ♎ 09/10 Music. Paramore. Stars. Rainbows. Guitars. Chocolates. Snickers. Cats. Kittens. Nail Polish. Magic. Fashion. High-Waist Pants. Art. Soft toys. Lollipops. Hard Candy. Twitter. Facebook. Blog. ...</content>
<nick>jannahward</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.fivestarwebsolution.com/?p=1160</link>
<time>1314005591</time>
<content>(And eat at your own risk — Fair Shake does not cure Spamburger-induced hysteria or deep-fried Snickers-psychosis.) Why You Should Care: “Fair Shake” takes the work out of hunting and gathering at the Minnesota State Fair. ...</content>
<nick>5*WebSolution</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://blog.3d.by/?p=90036</link>
<time>1314005396</time>
<content>addButton(vk_like_772325159,{pageUrl:http://ibigdan.livejournal.com/9121357.html,pageTitle:Шоколадки в разрезе,verb:1,pageDescription:Твикс Сникерс Сникерс баттер Марс Кит Кат Кит Кат белый шоколад Кит кат большой Hershey&#39;s - Air ...</content>
<nick>АжДваО</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://selling.in.ua/istorii-uspexa/istoriya-mars-ili-kak-sozdavalas-samaya-krupnaya-semejnaya-kompaniya.html</link>
<time>1314129543</time>
<content>Все это выльется в появление новых продуктов, среди которых будет и легендарный шоколадный батончик Snickers, который до сих пор является одним из флагманов продуктовой линейки Mars. Тем временем Форрест Марс заканчивает Йельский ...</content>
<nick>kashubama</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://salinapost.com/2011/08/23/breaking-ground-on-new-mm-factory-in-kansas/</link>
<time>1314128318</time>
<content>The plant will produce M&amp;Ms and Snickers candies. Kansas and local officials pledged incentives to help land the Mars project. The 350000-square-foot building will be constructed in the Kanza Fire Commerce Park near Topeka&#39;s Heartland ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://cameronwines.com/deep_roots/desperately-seeking-newsletters/</link>
<time>1314127283</time>
<content>Others immediately think of the dusty residue at the bottom of a box of Count Chocula cereal, or perhaps a flaming Snickers bar. The most fun you&#39;ll have with a wine app, though, will come courtesy of me, which is the creation of Gary ...</content>
<nick>John</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://bunnyanddolly.com/posts/levis-first-state-fair</link>
<time>1314120285</time>
<content>Deep fried Snickers on-a-stick (my fave!) Fried pineapple on-a-stick. Fried butter on-a-stick. Not everything we tasted came on a stick. We also enjoyed Saratoga chips and red velvet funnel cake, which tasted like regular funnel cake ...</content>
<nick>PJ / Dolly</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://mxibulkchocolate.jjbirden.com/2011/08/23/xocai-for-heart-health-in-eugene/</link>
<time>1314119683</time>
<content>Unfortunately, the processing methods used to make Snickers, Kit Kat, Hershey and the like strip the cocoa of its original nutrients. These popular brands of Cheshire chocolate also contain high levels of saturated fat, your heart&#39;s ...</content>
<nick>jjbirden270</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.drodd.com/lunch/?p=257</link>
<time>1314118886</time>
<content>8-23-11 – Cafe 150 – sandwich pretzels and snickers. http://www.symphonyiri.com/Insights/tabid/88/Default.aspx. « 8-19-11 – Slide Ride – 3 ribeye sliders. Comments are closed. Dr. Odd What&#39;s For Lunch is proudly powered by WordPress ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://sunonthesand.com/2011/jonti-to-release-debut-full-length-in-october/</link>
<time>1314118833</time>
<content>I try make simple pop songs with that same enthusiasm.” Full tracklist: 01 Hornets Nest 02 Koi Moons Daughter 03 Nightshift in Blue 04 Nodlews Way Home 05 Passaros 06 Snickers Hiss 07 Solar Smoking Dogs (Lucia) 08 Spooky Sport ...</content>
<nick>Vinh</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://martesnickers.wordpress.com/2011/08/23/23-augustus-2011/</link>
<time>1314118715</time>
<content>oké, ten eerste : ik heb twitter (@MarteSnickers), facebook (Marte Snickers), myspace (Marte Purnelle) &amp; tumblr (http://captainfishstick.tumblr.com). follow me of add me, please :&gt;. ten tweede : ik wil jullie nog eens vragen om reclame ...</content>
<nick>Marte Snickers</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.bengals101.com/2011/08/23/four-myths-about-the-cincinnati-bengals-in-2011/</link>
<time>1314119544</time>
<content>Perhaps it&#39;s that they were protecting a quarterback who looked like Betty White before eating the Snickers bar, or that the offensive coordinator was having receivers run 20 plus yard routes and calling play sequences that left the ...</content>
<nick>Chuck Chapman</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.mador-online.com/wordpress/funny-clip/thats-comedy-the-nets-1-joke-ebook-2.html</link>
<time>1314119379</time>
<content>That&#39;s Comedy! - The Net&#39;s #1 Joke eBook Over 340 Pages of Little Snickers, Medium-Sized Chuckles, and Great Big Belly Laughs. That&#39;s Comedy! - The Net&#39;s #1 Joke eBook.</content>
<nick>неизвестен</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://awakeanddreaming.org/?p=23424</link>
<time>1314118303</time>
<content>Aha! If the Genie in a lamp appears and gives me the option of lifetime supply,I&#39;d choose the following. Laptops &amp;external HDDs. PIZZAS Snickers bar ice Cream Vodka + Sprite since I am asthmatic,Asthalin inhalers popcorn apple juice ...</content>
<nick>Roshan</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://thecitylovesyou.com/urban/?p=44960</link>
<time>1314117973</time>
<content>Los otros 30 lugares serán mediante una invitación por parte de Snickers y Vans, ellos tendrán pase directo a la final en el Estadio Azteca y esta lista se dará a conocer el próximo 26 de agosto de 2011 en www.vans.com.mx ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://free-coupons-blog.com/?p=12685</link>
<time>1314117909</time>
<content>Bυу 2 Gеt 1 Free $0.50/2 Snickers Bars – Peelie οח Box, Bу Registers Final Price: $0.32 each wһеח уου bυу 3. Twizzlers 11 oz $2.59 $0.75/1 Twizzler Product frοm SS 6/26 οr 8/7. Final Price: $1.09, Aftеr Double ...</content>
<nick>jay</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://pahulu.blogspot.com/2011/08/summer-fun.html</link>
<time>1314117780</time>
<content>For his birthday we went to Tucanos for a late lunch and I made him a Snickers cheesecake. This is a random picture of Annie that really captures her personality. I asked her to go get her jammies and this is what she came back with. ...</content>
<nick>Heather</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://madbite.com/2011/08/23/the-inside-of-candy-bars/</link>
<time>1314117542</time>
<content>Mounds. Oh Henry! PayDay. Peanut Bar. Reese&#39;s White Chocolate Peanut Butter Cups. Snickers Almond. Snickers Dark. Snickers Peanut Butter. Sour Patch Kids. Swedish Fish. Take Five. Crunchie (UK). Toblerone. Tootsie Roll. Twix. Twizzlers ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://ezfundraiser.org/?p=4578</link>
<time>1314117496</time>
<content>Snickers Single Serve Candy Bar $0.99. Buy 2 Get 1 Free $0.50/2 Snickers Bars – Peelie on Box, By Registers Final Price: $0.32 each when you buy 3. Twizzlers 11 oz $2.59 $0.75/1 Twizzler Product from SS 6/26 or 8/7 ...</content>
<nick>неизвестен</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://filmdrunk.uproxx.com/2011/08/choice-quotes-from-esquires-ryan-gosling-profile</link>
<time>1314116983</time>
<content>Crapbasket. 08.23.11 at 1:29 pm. Crapbasket. Hey girl, that joke was just silly! **snickers**. Jessolido. 08.23.11 at 1:32 pm. Jessolido. They&#39;re not funny, but I save all my Dubble Bubble comics because someone took the time to write ...</content>
<nick>Vince Mancini</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://newrhymelines.wordpress.com/2011/08/23/a-toast-to-julie-and-jason/</link>
<time>1314116332</time>
<content>Julie has a teaching degree – And her friend Snickers the Cat. She loves collecting anything Cow – I felt you should know about that!! Julie has two sisters, Tara and Amy – Jason has a brother Mike. They are buying their first house ...</content>
<nick>rhymelines1</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.bakersroyale.com/cookies/cookies-cream-brownie-cookies/</link>
<time>1314116124</time>
<content>Suggested variations: Dried cherries and walnuts, toffee bits, crushed Oreo Cookies; and, of course the usual candy suspects-chopped Reese&#39;s Peanut Buttercups, Snickers, and Twix. I&#39;ve been trying something new by adding the salt and ...</content>
<nick>Naomi</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://mxibestchocolateintheworld.the-adam-green.biz/2011/08/23/hey-la-mesa-chocolate-for-healthy-digestion/</link>
<time>1314115810</time>
<content>Of course the Snickers and Hershey bars sold at any La Mesa grocery store are not the answer (hello diarrhea), however, Xocai XoBiotic squares deliver to your GI tract the microrganisms it needs for proper digestive function. ...</content>
<nick>adameap72</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.interest-free-credit-cardsnow.com/if-we-kiss-a-jonas-brothers-story-chapter-47</link>
<time>1314115204</time>
<content>Dad snickers with me and when we reach the bottom of the stairs, I see a box wrapped with pretty pale pink wrapping paper and a bow. I beam and walk over to it. “This it?” I ask in a dreamy voice. “Yes, go ahead… Open it…” Dad urges. ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://kineochurch.org/2011/08/23/pure-sex-part-2/</link>
<time>1314114905</time>
<content>Say, peanuts, I love peanuts, but I would never eat peanuts from a turd when I could just go to the store and get them in a nice, clean, new bag, or even in a Snickers. Peanuts were not meant to be eaten from turds. ...</content>
<nick>jskeens</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://teachingwithgraphicnovels.com/2011/08/23/review-fraggle-rock-vol-2-3/</link>
<time>1314113846</time>
<content>The cheerful colours are attractive and goofy names like Gobo, Wembley and Boober will no doubt elicit snickers and giggles from all corners of the classroom. Fraggle Rock Vol 2. #3 contains three separate stories, but my favourite for ...</content>
<nick>teachwithgraphicnovels</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://donhui.tk/?p=143</link>
<time>1314111966</time>
<content>That moff of disdain for her unbecoming snickers, gathered i turn into something that howled in the night. even finish drawing their own, they were seething masshe sent him a beseeching look of appeal. His dark eyterminal shortly,” ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://lones.biz/even-bad-boys-turn-good-in-vancouver-18</link>
<time>1314111634</time>
<content>But we&#39;re a little concerned about these 14-year-olds and their Facebook petition to replace Bob Costas with Justin Bieber, and Al Michaels with a really cute guinea pig named Snickers. © 2011 Wall Street Journal (www.wsj.com) ...</content>
<nick>KevMack</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.autisable.com/754421667/were-all-different-quirky-and-special---autism-is-no-different/</link>
<time>1314108000</time>
<content>Unfortunately, I found myself holding back snickers at her emotions instead of tears at the diagnosis. I had prepared myself for the diagnosis before it actually took place. His father and I were fine with it, after all why worry about ...</content>
<nick>неизвестен</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://httpmag.com/speedy-treatment-for-heart-attacks-called-finest-moment-medpage-today/2011/08/23/</link>
<time>1314107782</time>
<content>YEAH SNICKERS! :P. Reply. MrNarcko. August 23, 2011 • 11:13 am. i was crossing the street yesterday and u lagged..i got hit by a bus...fml. Reply. tetech12. August 23, 2011 • 12:10 pm. thumbs up if you tried to lick your elbow ...</content>
<nick>HTTPmag</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://food.lohudblogs.com/2011/08/23/uncle-louie-gs-opens-in-eastchester/</link>
<time>1314106733</time>
<content>Popular flavors include cappuccino chunk, Brooklyn cheesecake, vanilla Snickers, and apple pie ice cream, along with canola, chocolate Oreo, mudslide, rainbow and watermelon ices. They also make old-fashioned egg creams, ...</content>
<nick>Liz Johnson</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.buyshoptoday.com/snicker-candy-bar/snickers-tank-dress-tweenteen-costume-teen-13-16-b003iblrby/prices.html</link>
<time>1314095564</time>
<content>Online Shopping with great snicker candy bar, Compare prices for best cheap snicker candy bar, prices and reviews For sale 20-80% off.</content>
<nick>неизвестен</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://searchpoint.blogge.rs/archives/17718</link>
<time>1314089104</time>
<content>Sales:★★★★☆ Rasta Imposta Funny Snickers Candy Bar Dress Adult Halloween Costume Buy Compare Price Bestseller Shops Discount Now Free Shipping Rasta Imposta Funny Snickers Candy Bar Dress Adult Halloween Costume Tools Auto Industry ...</content>
<nick>new99</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.libo.ru/libo6285.html</link>
<time>1314086634</time>
<content>Твикс Твикс Сникерс Сникерс баттер Марс Кит Кат Кит Кат белый шоколад Кит кат большой Hershey&#39;s - Air Delight Тоблерон ? Буэно Виспа М&amp;Ms Сникерс дарк.</content>
<nick>hamster</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://phentermineblog.net/330/any-one-know-the-best-website-for-buying-phentermine-with-no-prescription-needed/</link>
<time>1314083435</time>
<content>Hotdogs cheeseburgers nachos snickers bars M&amp;Ms. Hotdogs cheeseburgers nachos snickers bars M&amp;Ms. Hotdogs cheeseburgers nachos snickers bars M&amp;Ms. Hotdogs cheeseburgers nachos snickers bars M&amp;Ms. Hotdogs cheeseburgers nachos snickers ...</content>
<nick>admin</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://www.dietsanddieting.mobi/1069/low-cal-snickers-pie/</link>
<time>1314080572</time>
<content>Low Cal Snickers Pie · raiderhost | August 23, 2011 | 0 Comments. 8 Servings. 1/2 Cup WW Chocolate Ice Milk (Softened) 1 Cup Light Cool Whip (thawed) 1 Pkg Sugarfree Chocolate Pudding (prepared) 1/4 Cup Crunchy Peanut Butter ...</content>
<nick>raiderhost</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://judithwesterfield.wordpress.com/2011/08/23/mini-snickers-caramel-cheesecakes/</link>
<time>1314070289</time>
<content>Place chopped Snickers Bars into a bowl, set aside for now. Place graham cracker crumbs, sugar and melted butter into a mixing bowl to combine. Spoon a couple spoonfuls of crumbs into each section of the muffin pan and press down and up ...</content>
<nick>creativitytothemax</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://android.mobile-cellulars.com/what-is-a-good-android-app-to-develop/</link>
<time>1314062265</time>
<content>@raehaan for number 36 he did snickers :D. raehaan August 23, 2011 at 12:09 pm. @aaronwashere100 number 36. aaronwashere100 August 23, 2011 at 12:53 pm. @raehaan ok umm which one did he count it as 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 ...</content>
<nick>неизвестен</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://snickitty.blogspot.com/2011/08/what-happened-to-aubrey-odays-boobs.html</link>
<time>1314061620</time>
<content>It got me thinking. Certainly it&#39;s a lot safer to do this via the sliders in Second Life than in real life. Full story here: http://entertainment.blogs.foxnews.com/2011/08/22/what-happened-to-aubrey-odays-body/. Posted by Snickers Snook ...</content>
<nick>Snickers Snook</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
<post>
<link>http://uppskriftasida.blogspot.com/2011/08/snickers-heilsukaka.html</link>
<time>1314048660</time>
<content>Hér er uppskrift að dásamlegri Snickers heilsuköku sem er æðislegur desert. Botn: 200 g döðlur 100 g möndlur 100 g kókosmjöl 1/2 tsk. vanilluduft eða dropar. Leggja þarf döðlurnar í bleyti í 10 mínútur og setja allt saman í ...</content>
<nick>...</nick>
<loc></loc>
</post>
